

#### Muhammad Zainal Arifin

#### Software Engineer

I'm currently working full time as a Software Engineer in a company in Yogyakarta (Cikajogja). Born in Karanganyar, Central Java, Indonesia, I Graduated from **VHS 2 Karanganyar** at 2021 as Software Engineering student, i'm interested in the world of technology, especially programming. I have experience in several projects in creating, developing web-based and mobile-based applications.

https://muhamadzain-dev.vercel.app/

in in/muhammad-zainal-arifin/ Tainal21 M Zainalarifin080718@gmail.com

# Skills



#### Other Skills

- Time Management
- Team Work
- High willingness to learn. etc

### Languages

- Indonesia Native
- English Passive

## Work Experience



# Software Engineer CV. Cipa Karya Informatika (Cikajogja)

June 2021 - Present Sleman, Yogyakarta I work as a software engineer in a software company, and I have contributed to several projects such as

- "SindegaJawi" in Satpol PP DIY Information system
- JTL Express Shipper Area with Codeigniter 3
- Rest API for JTL Express Shipper Area with Lumen Framework
- JTL Express Cargo System (Codeigniter 3),
- Build a new feature "Undelivery" on APK Kurir JTLExpress (Kotlin)
- Official Android Apps JTL Express ( Kotlin )



# Web Developer (Intern) CV. Kadang Koding Indonesia

January 2020 - April 2020 Surakarta, Jawa Tengah I became a participant in the school internship program, in this internship I build

- Company Profile website using wordpress CMS,
- Build an Online Wedding Invitation Management System using Laravel
- Build Rest API for inventory POS using Laravel

#### Education

2018 - 2020

SMKN 2 Karanganyar Software Engineering

### **Academic Achievement**

2021

Top 16 in Web Technologies Skill Competition
Student Competency Competition
(LKS SMK Tingkat Provinsi Jawa Tengah 2021)